I don't know, I just remember it being so much brighter, I guess
cigarette ash like wildfire burning holes in the night time
open scars feel like barbed wire white lights flying high like a ceasefire
drop of flags on the shoreline this is as far as I can feel right
because while you don't know can haunt you and all we ever wanted was sunlight and honesty
highlights to wanna repeat let's get away from here and live like the movies do I won't mind
when it's over at least I didn't think for a while don't drag it out living like what doesn't mean
so let's run make a great escape and I'll be waiting outside for the getaway it doesn't
matter who we are we'll keep running through the dark and all that we need is another day
we can slow down because tomorrow is a mile away and live like shooting stars
because happy endings hardest to say yeah sunsets and power lines making a break for the other side
heading out to where the sun shines 45 millimeter rolling like we lost time
polaroids and outcasts rather burn out young and grow fast and we could be forever future bound
because all I need is time and now and I could leave this past behind me and maybe I'll see
a way for me to stay when there's so much out there so I'll live forgetting for the time being
and I won't mind when it's over at least I didn't think for a while
so let's run make a great escape and I'll be waiting outside for the getaway it doesn't matter
who we are we'll keep running through the dark and all that we need is another day we can slow down
because tomorrow is a mile away and live like shooting stars because everything was never the
same and I wanna let you know I wanna let you go but I just can't bring myself to speak but this
is how it goes the end credits they're all this bridge was built over kerosene but we can watch
oh
make a great escape and I'll be waiting outside for the getaway it doesn't matter who we are
running through the dark and all I ever need is another day we can slow down because tomorrow is
in my way